export const mandarinDeck = [
    {
        "Question": "你好！",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ hǎo!",
        "Answer": "Hello!"
    },
    {
        "Question": "你好吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ hǎo ma?",
        "Answer": "How are you?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "谢谢。",
        "Pinyin": "Xièxie.",
        "Answer": "Thank you."
    },
    {
        "Question": "不客气。",
        "Pinyin": "Bú kèqi.",
        "Answer": "You're welcome."
    },
    {
        "Question": "对不起。",
        "Pinyin": "Duìbuqǐ.",
        "Answer": "Excuse me."
    },
    {
        "Question": "再见！",
        "Pinyin": "Zàijiàn!",
        "Answer": "Goodbye!"
    },
    {
        "Question": "回头见。",
        "Pinyin": "Huítóu jiàn.",
        "Answer": "See you later."
    },
    {
        "Question": "你叫什么名字？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ jiào shénme míngzi?",
        "Answer": "What is your name?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我叫...",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ jiào...",
        "Answer": "My name is..."
    },
    {
        "Question": "厕所在哪里？",
        "Pinyin": "Cèsuǒ zài nǎli?",
        "Answer": "Where is the bathroom?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我不明白。",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ bù míngbai.",
        "Answer": "I don't understand."
    },
    {
        "Question": "这个多少钱？",
        "Pinyin": "Zhège duōshao qián?",
        "Answer": "How much does it cost?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "你会说英语吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ huì shuō Yīngyǔ ma?",
        "Answer": "Do you speak English?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "这是什么意思？",
        "Pinyin": "Zhè shì shénme yìsi?",
        "Answer": "What does it mean?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我饿了。",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ è le.",
        "Answer": "I'm hungry."
    },
    {
        "Question": "我渴了。",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ kě le.",
        "Answer": "I'm thirsty."
    },
    {
        "Question": "哪里可以找到餐馆？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǎli kěyǐ zhǎodào cānguǎn?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find a restaurant?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我迷路了。",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ mílù le.",
        "Answer": "I'm lost."
    },
    {
        "Question": "请帮帮我。",
        "Pinyin": "Qǐng bāng bāng wǒ.",
        "Answer": "Please help me."
    },
    {
        "Question": "怎么去...？",
        "Pinyin": "Zěnme qù...?",
        "Answer": "How do I get to...?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "银行在哪里？",
        "Pinyin": "Yínháng zài nǎli?",
        "Answer": "Where is the bank?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "附近有餐馆吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Fùjìn yǒu cānguǎn ma?",
        "Answer": "Are there any restaurants nearby?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "怎么去博物馆？",
        "Pinyin": "Zěnme qù bówùguǎn?",
        "Answer": "How do I get to the museum?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我迷路了。你能帮我找到酒店吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ mílù le. Nǐ néng bāng wǒ zhǎodào jiǔdiàn ma?",
        "Answer": "I'm lost. Can you help me find the hotel?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "你推荐这座城市的哪些景点？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ tuījiàn zhè zuò chéngshì de nǎxiē jǐngdiǎn?",
        "Answer": "What do you recommend visiting in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "如何预订餐馆的座位？",
        "Pinyin": "Rúhé yùdìng cānguǎn de zuòwèi?",
        "Answer": "How do I book a table at a restaurant?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我可以在哪找到药店？",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ kěyǐ zài nǎ zhǎodào yàodiàn?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find a pharmacy?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "商店营业时间是几点？",
        "Pinyin": "Shāngdiàn yíngyè shíjiān shì jǐ diǎn?",
        "Answer": "What are the store's working hours?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我想买个纪念品。",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ xiǎng mǎi gè jìniànpǐn.",
        "Answer": "I would like to buy a souvenir."
    },
    {
        "Question": "你最喜欢这座城市的哪家餐馆？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ zuì xǐhuan zhè zuò chéngshì de nǎ jiā cānguǎn?",
        "Answer": "What's your favorite restaurant in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "你能帮我拍张照片吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ néng bāng wǒ pāi zhāng zhàopiàn ma?",
        "Answer": "Can you take a photo of me, please?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "哪里可以去听音乐会？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǎli kěyǐ qù tīng yīnyuèhuì?",
        "Answer": "Where can I go for a concert?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "最近的公园有多远？",
        "Pinyin": "Zuìjìn de gōngyuán yǒu duō yuǎn?",
        "Answer": "How far is the nearest park?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我在哪里可以找到旅游景点的信息？",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ zài nǎli kěyǐ zhǎodào lǚyóu jǐngdiǎn de xìnxī?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find information about tourist attractions?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "我可以叫一辆出租车吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Wǒ kěyǐ jiào yí liàng chūzūchē ma?",
        "Answer": "Can I order a taxi?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "这座城市最著名的博物馆是哪个？",
        "Pinyin": "Zhè zuò chéngshì zuì zhùmíng de bówùguǎn shì nǎge?",
        "Answer": "What is the most famous museum in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "你有推荐的本地咖啡馆吗？",
        "Pinyin": "Nǐ yǒu tuījiàn de běndì kāfēiguǎn ma?",
        "Answer": "Do you have any recommendations for local cafes?"
    }
];
